{
  "Padawan": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Millenium Falcon",
      "allAnswers": ["X-Wing", "Razor Crest", "Millenium Falcon"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Anakin Skywalker grew up to be who?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader",
      "allAnswers": ["Darth Maul", "Darth Vader", "Count Dooku"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who are the two droids that appear in every Star Wars film?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "R2-D2 & C-3PO",
      "allAnswers": ["BB-8 & R2-D2", "C-3PO & BB-8", "R2-D2 & C-3PO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Luke Skywalker's home planet",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Tatooine",
      "allAnswers": ["Alderaan", "Tatooine", "Hoth", "Coruscant"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary weapon used by Jedi Knights and Sith Lords?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Lightsaber",
      "allAnswers": ["Lightsaber", "Phaser", "Blaster", "Ion Cannon"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the main antagonist in the original Star Wars trilogy",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Grand Moff Tarkin",
        "Jabba the Hutt",
        "Emperor Palpatine",
        "Darth Vader"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the nickname given to the Millennium Falcon's co-pilot",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Chewie",
      "allAnswers": ["R2-D2", "Chewie", "C-3PO", "BB-8"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the iconic short green creature?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Yoda",
      "allAnswers": ["Jar-Jar Binks", "Yoda", "R2-D2", "Chewbacca"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who wears the iconic white helmets?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Stormtroopers",
      "allAnswers": ["Ewoks", "Gungans", "Droids", "Stormtroopes"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who killed Han Solo?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Padawan",
      "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren",
      "allAnswers": ["Kylo Ren", "Snoke", "R2-D2"]
    }
  ],
  "JediKnight": [
    {
      "question": "What is C-3PO?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Droid",
      "allAnswers": ["Robot", "AI", "Droid"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Baby Yoda's real name?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Grogu",
      "allAnswers": ["Yoda Jr", "Grogu", "Rancorn"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the Supreme Chancellor of the Galactic Republic before becoming the Sith Lord Darth Sidious?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Palpatine",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Bail Organa",
        "Palpatine",
        "Sheev Palpatine",
        "Jar Jar Binks"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which character says the iconic line: 'I find your lack of faith disturbing'?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Emperor Palpatine",
        "Grand Moff Tarkin",
        "Darth Maul",
        "Darth Vader"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the crime syndicate led by Jabba the Hutt?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Hutt Cartel",
      "allAnswers": ["Black Sun", "Crimson Dawn", "Hutt Cartel", "Death Watch"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which character is known for the line: 'Do or do not. There is no try.' ?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Yoda",
      "allAnswers": ["Qui-Gon Jinn", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Yoda", "Luke Skywalker"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the founder and leader of the Knights of Ren?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren",
      "allAnswers": ["Snoke", "Kylo Ren", "Captain Phasma", "General Hux"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first Jedi to be seen using a double-bladed lightsaber in the Star Wars films?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Darth Maul",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Qui-Gon Jinn",
        "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
        "Count Dooku",
        "Darth Maul"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Rebel Alliance's base on the ice planet Hoth?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Echo Base",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Base Alpha",
        "Rebel Outpost 417",
        "Echo Base",
        "Blue Squadron Base"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who initiated Order 66?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "JediKnight",
      "correctAnswer": "Darth Sidious",
      "allAnswers": ["Darth Vader", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Darth Sidious"]
    }
  ],
  "Grandmaster": [
    {
      "question": "What is Anakin Skywalker midi chlorian count?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "27000",
      "allAnswers": ["25000", "27000", "29000"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who invented the rule of two?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Darth Bane",
      "allAnswers": ["Darth Sidious", "Darth Plagueis", "Darth Bane"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Mandalorian's ship?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Razor Crest",
      "allAnswers": ["Millenium Falcon", "Razor Crest", "Death Star", "B-Wing"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first character to speak in the original 1977 'Star War' film?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia",
      "allAnswers": ["C-3PO", "Princess Leia", "Darth Vader", "Admiral Motti"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the original owner of the Millennium Falcon before it comes into Han Solo's possession?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Lando Calrissian",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Lando Calrissian",
        "Chewbacca",
        "Qui-Gon Jinn",
        "Wedge Antilles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Finn's Stormtrooper number?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "FN-2187",
      "allAnswers": ["FN-2187", "NF-5271", "FN-3147", "NF-7"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was responsible for killing the Jedi Younglings in 'Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith'?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Anakin Skywalker",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Darth Vader",
        "Count Dooku",
        "General Grievous",
        "Anakin Skywalker"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Anakins rival in the pod race from Episode I?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Sebulba",
      "allAnswers": ["Cad Bane", "Watto", "Sebulba", "Jabba the Hutt"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the deadly disease that affects the Clones in the Clone Wars series?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Clone Syndrome",
      "allAnswers": [
        "Clone Syndrome",
        "Kaminoan Fever",
        "Clone Sickness",
        "Clone Trooper Degeneration"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Where do the rebels celebrate the fall of the Empire?",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Grandmaster",
      "correctAnswer": "Endor",
      "allAnswers": ["Tatooine", "Endor", "Coruscant"]
    }
  ]
}
